[Music]
Busing stocks, yes, news stocks,
where we see action due to the news.
What should be your reaction?
Arun ji will tell you this, and we will tell you the news.
What should be the strategy in it?
You will decide whether to buy or sell. So let's
start this segment of the program
and bring you the first company. Let me
tell you that he has resigned
and the board of Paytm Bank will be reconstituted.
Vijay Shekhar Sharma has
resigned as the Chairman of Paytm Bank and
former Central Bank Chairman Srinivas
Sridhar will now be included in the board. So a
lot of changes are happening
and due to all this, today we are seeing a
strength of around half a percent
in the initial trading session.
[Music]
Well, when we made the news, the
strength was around half a percent and now we are seeing a
rise of more than 2 percent, the level of 437 is visible.
What does the future look like? Sir, there is a
lot of confusion. Although
those who left have left till now, but
still many people are trying to bottom fish.
Many people have positions at higher
prices and they are taking advantage of this.  We are waiting for
our price to come.
What advice would you give on Paytm at this time?
Vipul ji, you asked a very interesting question
and by taking two minutes, I
want to explain to the viewer that Paytm has
two businesses. The first one is that
it gives you a wallet. You
can make many types of payments from that wallet
and you can also do direct work by linking your bank account.
This work of making payments was
not stopped anywhere. The only
restriction that was imposed was on Paytm's
payments bank where your wallet
money was deposited.
RBI stopped this work. Many
questions were
asked within it and many types of negative news also came.
When RBI
banned one by one what is called them from
opening new accounts and continuing them, since then there has been a
lot of commotion in this city.
Now they were told that you are not able to handle this bank,
you should take care of your core business
and this work that you were doing of
maintaining balances and dealing with other banks.  Also, you can make
their accounts.
Paytm showed some negligence in doing this and did
not take any action against it. Vijay Shekhar
Sharma ji, who calls himself Vijay, could
not use the new system in it, he did
not accept it, finally he went and
designed it yesterday. Now this Paytm Bank will start
improving on its own, so this business will also get
better in the coming time.
As far as Paytm's work is concerned, its jingle
comes in Paytm karo, it is business as usual.
So I think that if those who have done bottom
fishing become a little careful, then
some money can definitely be made from here.
Okay, and those who are stuck in the higher levels,
what should they wait for?
I do not know the definition of higher because this stock
came from a price above 000. Now if you
talk about 500, 550, then that price may
come in some time, but if your
purchase is around a thousand rupees, then it will take a
lot of time to come. It will take time. Okay,
let's be clear.  This is a good thing.
Let's
bring the next company to the screen. There was news on Cello Word today,
and let's see what news there is.
Here, Motilal Oswal has
said that they have started coverage on the company,
given a buy rating, and also
set a target of 00% on Cello Word.
This IPO also came out recently, and
we discussed it in great detail.
Currently, there are about six brokerage houses
that have given a buy rating on Cello Word,
and there is not a single brokerage house
that has a sell rating.
All these things are such that due to this, we are seeing
that today a momentum is being seen within the stock. The
rise around 4F is
still visible. The level of 877 is being
seen.
Sir, due to the coverage started by many brokerage houses in Cello Word,
especially Motilal Oswal has
started its coverage today, a
positive momentum is seen building here.
How are you watching?  Hello
Sir, I agree with you that do
you see a target of 1100 in the coming time?
Sir, see, the
price target on this company,
different brokerages have different lagging levels
and the time taken for reaching that level is
also different. What
I agree with is that the company is good, the
performance of the company is positive, growth is being seen
and in the coming time, the
price of its share will increase. It is a little difficult for me to predict how much it will reach in how much time. But if you take the price target of
10 to 12 percent
growth in the company within the next six to 12 months, then
you will definitely get it. The sector is good, it is a
consumer industry sector and this
company also manufactures pens, which it used to manufacture earlier
and it had sold its plant to a French
company, so it has completely come back into this business
and this will be a big growth for it
in the coming time. Now, this company,
which is a business of its class, is also setting up a new factory
in Rajasthan, which I think will happen
in the next two to three months.  If it starts, then
take it as a positive for a company. In the meantime, let's bring the next company and that
is Sikachi Industries.
Momentum is also seen building in Sikachi Industries today
and let's bring the news that is here
on the screen and from there try to understand what strategy should be adopted in this Sikachi Industries right now. Let's bring this company on the screen. So, let's
tell you about Sikachi Industries, the news is that the
company has done a joint venture to enter the food and pharma business of UAE and this JV has been done by the
company's subsidiary company Saga Mina A
Fusco and this JV has been done with a
company named I Consult from UAE.
Sikachi's share in this JV will be
around 75 percent and the other
company will have 25 percent and the company
expects that by 2029, the
company has expected sales of around Rs 5.4 crore from this JV.
Today
in the stock, we were seeing that when
in the initial trading session  A rally of over 2% was
seen in Siga, and
if we look now, it has eased a bit from the higher levels,
but still, the
price is seen here at around 1 paise above, at 9080 paise.
Sir, if you track, I would
like to know your opinion on Sigaji Industries. Now, the company is going to enter the UAE business, especially
in the food and pharma sector.
In the last six months, a return of 140% has been
seen here.
So look at the business of this company, it
manufactures a chemical product connected to paper and pulp, which is
used in the food industry and pharma industry.
It wants to expand the same thing in the UAE,
and for that, it has
collaborated with a UAE company. This is a good
thing for this company, but looking at the price
run-up that has happened in the last three to four months, it
seems that the price has
increased a bit too much. While making a new investment, investors
should think a little about whether the
momentum has increased too much or
not. If they invest with this in mind, then it will be
profitable. So, let's go then.  At
the moment, this opinion is
coming out here. Let's bring the next company
to the screen and see
what news is there and what impact the news is being
seen. ICICI Lombard. Today
we saw that there is
some strength in the insurance sector, but the
news here is that ICICI Bank has
increased its stake in ICICI Lombard. Through a block deal, ICICI
Bank has bought 1.4 percent stake. Let us
tell you that Indian Enterprise has
sold this stake and
ICICI Bank has increased its stake through this block deal.
In the last one month, we have seen that the
stock has seen a rally of around 15 percent.
If we talk about today,
what is the situation?
Even today, in the initial trading area, we were seeing
that there was strength around 3 percent.
Now it is trading above 45 percent. The level of 1722 is
visible here. Sir,
ICICI Lombard is in good momentum today. It is
such a bank that it has
increased its stake here.
If we look at the last six months, there is a rally of around  The
returns have been around 29-30 per cent but other
insurance companies are also in momentum today.
New India Insurance is in good momentum today. There is a
boom in Ase Lord. What would be
your opinion on the insurance sector and also your
comment on ICICI Lombard,
Vipul ji. If you talk about the insurance sector,
this insurance is quite under-
penetrated in India and since Covid
came and went, one thing has become certain
in the country that the general public wants to have
some health insurance.
Awareness has increased. Penetration of
insurance, which is very full in India, has
also seen some growth.
ICICI Prudential and ICICI
Lombard are also such companies in which they are
seeing growth
and this block deal that happened today was
between two institutional investors.
It is a different matter that the buyer in that is the
promoter of the company, so this is a good
thing. A lot of consolidation is happening in the sector
and good growth is being seen in insurance.
If you look at
LIC also, if you  Talking about the performance, it was quite
disappointing
after listing and that stock also rose significantly today,
seeing it above the issue price and is now
trading comfortably above it. This is our opinion at the
moment and in the meantime
let's come to the next company and take a
look at eMyTrip to see
what news has come out there and why
this stock is seen rising. Let us
tell you that a big block deal was seen in the company's stock today
and let us
show you at what price this block deal has happened. Actually, here Minerva
Ventures Fund has bought about 0.5 percent stake in the company's shares
and this share has been bought.
Minerva has bought 90 lakh shares of the company for Rs 4.87 crore and
this deal was seen happening at a price of 8.75 paise per share
and due to this, today we were seeing
that a good momentum was seen building in eTrip.  There was a
rally of more than 3 in the trading session
but now the stock has softened from the upper levels
but the rally of 2 is still there, the
price around 9 is being seen here
Sir, how are you looking at Easy Trip Planner
and what strategy should be adopted here, there has been a slight
underperformance as per the
G20 and all the things that happened, the
delivery from Easy Trip was not as expected, Sir,
you are right Vipul ji, but keep one thing in mind, whatever
this
company says has always been in the headlines,
in the last two-three months, first of all, in the
discussions that took place regarding Lakshadweep and Maldives,
this company first took a decision
that it will no longer sell tour programs of Maldives, it will
promote Lakshadweep,
then it expressed its desire to invest in a hotel in Ayodhya
and was making a joint venture for that,
now this is a kind of
block deal in this, so this company has been
in the headlines for a good while, something or the other keeps happening in this, whatever a
little bit is
said in this  Interest hasn't come in, but
both volume and volume have been good for the company. The
volume you get while being in the headlines
provides a good opportunity for investing. So, if you invest in it,
book your profit when the price target is achieved. Then find a new entry
level. That way, you'll be able to make more money. Yes, let's
move ahead and
bring the next company, which is also
related to the hospital industry.
Let's bring Lemon Tree shares. What's the news on Lemon Tree? The
news on Lemon Tree is that the
company has signed an agreement to acquire properties in Andhra Pradesh and Rajasthan. Let us
tell you that the company expects both hotels in both locations to
open by FY 26.
Apart from this, the hotel in Sankhwas Garh will have
51 rooms, which will be a Rajasthan
property. Apart from this, the hotel in Vijayawada,
which is being acquired in Andhra Pradesh, will have
44 rooms.
Today, we are seeing a rise of around 1% in the company's shares
due to the new hotel expansion plan.  If we
look at it now, we are still seeing the same
strength of about half a pip. The
level of 141-142 is visible in the levy.
Sir, what would be your opinion on levy,
Sir, should we invest here right now?
Vipul ji, this
hospitality sector has been quite interesting. If you
look at it, recently, in about two and a half
months, three hospitality companies have
entered the stock market. Two of them are
listed, one is Sami Hotels and the other is Park Hotels, and
tomorrow, one company will be listed, that is your
Juniper Hotels. As it is said that
after Covid, a revenge travel was seen
in India and there has been a huge increase in the tariffs of hotels.
Despite this, hotel availability has
reduced considerably and the demand is very high.
Due to this,
all the companies in the hospitality sector have seen a good
growth. Lemon Tree is also a
city which I had recommended some time
ago and that
call was closed out after achieving the price target. I think this
company has a bright future going forward.  It is good that
you often get entry levels in these stocks
and like three days ago the market
was in bad shape, there was a big correction in the market,
such is the day when you should invest in your
selected stocks which you have kept aside,
yes, in the meantime, a lot of
stocks were discussed in Bajrang, so that's all
for now in Bajrang stocks
[Sangeet]